<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:24:14 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HUGO static site generator</title>
      <link>/post/other/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/other/hugo/</guid>
      <description>I guess some of you have heard about HUGO and how it is a great tool for building static websites. Personally I have used it for creating this blog and also for my father&amp;rsquo;s company website ptaino.com. I don&amp;rsquo;t have any prior experience with other static generation tools so I am not in a position to compare it to other solutions like Jekyll. What I can share with you though is my personal experience after using it, why I love it and tips to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JShell</title>
      <link>/post/java/java_9/jshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 20:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/java/java_9/jshell/</guid>
      <description>For those who haven&amp;rsquo;t heard the news, Java has officially its own shell, named (obviously) JShell since Java 9. It is a REPL type of environment where you type your code in the command line interface and see the results immediately on your screen. This is a good way to test simple programming concepts and ideas without the inherited boilerplate verbosity, which JUnit or main function has. Also semicolons in the end are optional!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for first time presenters</title>
      <link>/post/other/tips_for_first_time_presenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 22:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/other/tips_for_first_time_presenters/</guid>
      <description>Well last week, I had the pleasure and honor to present in a conference for the first time. It was GeeCon Prague and more details about my talk can be found here. Following, you can find my tips for those who want to start presenting but don&amp;rsquo;t have any prior experience.
 Number one and most important have a story to share about something you love doing or something that helped you solve problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My talk at GeeCon Prague 2018</title>
      <link>/post/geecon/geecon_prague_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 20:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/geecon/geecon_prague_2018/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday on October 18th, I had the pleasure and excitement to present for the first time in a conference! It was GeeCon Prague and the organization plus the quality of the talks was really good, I highly recommend it to everyone! Something that I found to be really productive was that most speakers had a practical approach to their presentations, meaning a lot of code snippets and discussion with the crowd was there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java 10 &#43; var = L.F.E. </title>
      <link>/post/java/java_10/var/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/java/java_10/var/</guid>
      <description>New variable type named &amp;lsquo;var&amp;rsquo; in Java 10? Have we started turning into JavaScript anarchists? Has its very substance been polluted by Kotlin enthusiasts? Should we all worry by this new &amp;ldquo;feature&amp;rdquo; (are we sure its not a bug?) or could there be any benefits from using &amp;lsquo;var&amp;rsquo; in our code?
Var is used for type inference in Java and helps reduce the verbosity of the language. This means you are able to omit variables&amp;rsquo; type, as it will be inferred by the compiler by looking at the right hand part of the assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Don&#39;t Make Me Think&#39; book review</title>
      <link>/post/books/dont_make_me_think/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 20:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/books/dont_make_me_think/</guid>
      <description>After reading &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Make Me Think&amp;rsquo; from Steve Krug I felt like Daniel-San from the movie &amp;ldquo;Karate Kid&amp;rdquo;. One scene shows Daniel&amp;rsquo;s frustration, after painting mister Miyagi&amp;rsquo;s fence for four days straight without learning anything about Karate. His initial frustration goes away upon realizing his mastery of the fundamentals. So what does both the movie and book have in common? You guesses it right, its all about the fundamentals! Plus you get a bit of secret sauce&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JCrete 2018</title>
      <link>/post/jcrete/jcrete_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 20:24:14 +0300</pubDate>
      <author>nomikosi@thefuriousprogrammer.com (Iakovos Nomikos)</author>
      <guid>/post/jcrete/jcrete_2018/</guid>
      <description>Last July I had the opportunity to make three of my life dreams come true. First was taking a hike to Verliga dragonlake in Pindos, Greece. The second was watching Justice live which happened during We Are Electric festival in Holland. The third and most relative to this blog was attending JCrete unconference.
During my 4 year professional experience as a java developer, I have been to many conferences and meetings across Greece.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>